<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Jim Grange on Jim Grange</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Jim Grange on Jim Grange</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>&amp;copy; 2018</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 20 Apr 2016 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>A new website</title>
      <link>/post/a-new-website/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/a-new-website/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I have spent the past day or so transporting my acedemic website from &lt;a href=&#34;https://jimgrange.wordpress.com&#34;&gt;Wordpress&lt;/a&gt; to the current website, which is written using the (superb!) &lt;a href=&#34;https://bookdown.org/yihui/blogdown/&#34;&gt;R package ‘blogdown’&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I made the change for a variety of reasons:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;I am now able to use R for &lt;em&gt;most&lt;/em&gt; things—analysis, simulations, writing papers using &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/crsh/papaja&#34;&gt;papaja&lt;/a&gt; and now my website—making my workflow more efficient (and high on the nerd-scale).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;I could never really get my wordpress site to look sleek and professional. Using R and blogdown I was able to utilise the &lt;a href=&#34;https://themes.gohugo.io/&#34;&gt;Hugo website templates&lt;/a&gt;, which look very nice. (The current versio of my website uses the &lt;a href=&#34;https://themes.gohugo.io/academic/&#34;&gt;Hugo Academic theme&lt;/a&gt;.)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;As the blog is written in R and blogdown, it means that all the content &amp;amp; code behind it can be made freely available. You can see the Github page for the code of my website &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/JimGrange/website&#34;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;The blog posts on my previous site which I enjoyed writing the most had R demonstrations in them. As blogdown uses markdown, I can now write blog posts using markdown meaning I can integrate R code into the blog post! Not just that, plots are automatically integrated into the blog! Observe thus!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;pre class=&#34;r&#34;&gt;&lt;code&gt;library(ggplot2)
ggplot(faithfuld, aes(waiting, eruptions)) +
  geom_raster(aes(fill = density)) +
  scale_fill_distiller(palette = &amp;quot;Spectral&amp;quot;)&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;/post/2018-04-20-a-new-website_files/figure-html/unnamed-chunk-1-1.png&#34; width=&#34;672&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;What other reasons did I need?&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cognitive Control Processes</title>
      <link>/project/cognitive_control/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Feb 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/project/cognitive_control/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;current-projects&#34;&gt;Current Projects:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;#task_switching&#34;&gt;Task Switching&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;#memory_cognitive_control&#34;&gt;Memory &amp;amp; Cognitive Control&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;task_switching&#34;&gt;Task Switching&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Humans live in an increasingly busy, multi-task environment which often requires frequent switching between different cognitive operations and tasks. Driving, for example, presents us with an incredibly complex environment wherein many sub-tasks&amp;mdash;e.g. speed monitoring, interpretation of abstract road signs, planning the best route etc.&amp;mdash;must be organised and deployed appropriately in order to arrive at our destination safely. Yet, despite the complexity, humans are able to act efficiently in a goal-directed manner. The question thus arises as to how humans are able to organise and control the selection and deployment of on-going cognitive processes to ensure successful performance in multi-task environments.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Our work focusses on how this control is achieved. In particular, much of our work has focussed on one mechanism thought to aid control during task switching: Inhibition of competing tasks. When switching from one task to another, the persisting activation of the now-irrelevant task can interfere with the selection of the new task. There is good evidence that the cognitive system overcomes this problem by inhibiting (i.e., suppressing) the activation of recently performed tasks, enabling efficient selection of the new task.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What is the nature of this inhibition? What cognitive representations does it act on? How does the cognitive system know what &amp;amp; when to inhibit? What drives individual differences in inhibition?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;representative-publications&#34;&gt;Representative Publications&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Kowalczyk, A., &amp;amp; &lt;strong&gt;Grange, J.A.&lt;/strong&gt; (2017). Inhibition in task switching: The reliability of the n&amp;ndash;2 repetition cost. &lt;em&gt;Quarterly Journal of Experimental Psychology, 70&lt;/em&gt;, 2419&amp;ndash;2433. &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.jimgrange.org/publication/kowalczyk-inhibition_reliability/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;(Link)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;

&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Grange, J.A.,&lt;/strong&gt; &amp;amp; Juvina, I. (2015). The effect of practice on n&amp;ndash;2 repetition costs in set switching. &lt;em&gt;Acta Psychologica, 154&lt;/em&gt;, 14&amp;ndash;25. &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.jimgrange.org/publication/Grange-inhibition_practice/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;(Link)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;

&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Grange, J.A.,&lt;/strong&gt; &amp;amp; Houghton, G. (Eds.). &lt;em&gt;Task switching and cognitive control&lt;/em&gt;. New York, NY: Oxford University Press. &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.jimgrange.org/publication/grange-task_switching_book/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;(Link)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;

&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Grange, J.A.,&lt;/strong&gt; Juvina, I., &amp;amp; Houghton, G. (2013). On costs and benefits of n&amp;ndash;2 repetition costs in task switching: Toward a behavioral marker of cognitive inhibition. &lt;em&gt;Psychological Research, 77&lt;/em&gt;, 211&amp;ndash;222. &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.jimgrange.org/publication/grange-costs_benefits_inhibition_model/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;(Link)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;

&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Grange, J.A.,&lt;/strong&gt; &amp;amp; Houghton, G. (2010). Heightened conflict in cue&amp;ndash;target translation increases backward inhibition in set switching. &lt;em&gt;Journal of Experimental Psychology: Learning, Memory, &amp;amp; Cognition, 36&lt;/em&gt;, 1003&amp;ndash;1009 &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.jimgrange.org/publication/grange-negative_transfer/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;(Link)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;memory_cognitive_control&#34;&gt;Memory &amp;amp; Cognitive Control&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Although memory and cognitive control are typically treated (and researched) as separate sub-disciplines in cognitive psychology, there is plenty of evidence that they interact. I have become interested in what role memory retrieval plays in cognitive control during task switching.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In a typical task switching experiment, a participant might be presented with a single digit (e.g., &amp;ldquo;9&amp;rdquo;) and be asked to judge whether it is odd/even or lower/higher than 5 (and make a speeded response accordingly). Whilst of course participants could solve these tasks using a relatively involved algorithm (e.g., to decide if a number is odd, see if it is divisible by 2), participants could also just retrieve the correct answer from memory.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There is evidence that this memory retrieval is automatic (see for example the classic paper by &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.psy.vanderbilt.edu/faculty/logan/1988LoganPR.pdf&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Logan, 1998&lt;/a&gt;): When presented with a stimulus, the cognitive system automatically retrieves all responses previously associated with that stimulus. Such &lt;em&gt;episodic retrieval&lt;/em&gt; is obviously very useful in some circumstances, allowing us to act on auto-pilot. However, if multiple&amp;mdash;conflicting&amp;mdash;responses have been associated with the same stimulus, this can often lead to difficulties in selecting the most appropriate action.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My work has investigated how memory retrieval interacts with cognitive control in task switching. I have shown that successful episodic retrieval depends on how distinctive that episodic trace is in long term memory (Grange &amp;amp; Cross, 2015). In this work I also extended a successful model from the memory literature &lt;a href=&#34;http://psycnet.apa.org/fulltext/2007-10421-001.html&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;(SIMPLE; Brown et al., 2007)&lt;/a&gt; to the task switching paradigm to predict both mean response times &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.jimgrange.org/publication/Grange-temporal_distinctiveness/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;(Grange &amp;amp; Cross, 2015)&lt;/a&gt; and their distributions &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.jimgrange.org/publication/Grange-mixture_dist/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;(Grange, 2016)&lt;/a&gt;. I have also shown that measures of inhibition in task switching can also largely be explained by episodic memory processes &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.jimgrange.org/publication/episodic_retrieval/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;(Grange et al., 2017)&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;representative-publications-1&#34;&gt;Representative Publications&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Grange, J.A.,&lt;/strong&gt; Kowalczyk, A., &amp;amp; O&amp;rsquo;Loughlin, R. (2017). The effect of episodic retrieval on inhibition in task switching. &lt;em&gt;Journal of Experimental Psychology: Human Perception &amp;amp; Performance, 43&lt;/em&gt;, 1568&amp;ndash;1583. &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.jimgrange.org/publication/episodic_retrieval/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;(Link)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;

&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Grange, J.A.&lt;/strong&gt; (2016). Temporal distinctiveness in task switching: Assessing the mixture-distribution assumption. &lt;em&gt;Frontiers in Cognition, 7&lt;/em&gt;:251. &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.jimgrange.org/publication/Grange-mixture_dist/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;(Link)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;

&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Grange, J.A.,&lt;/strong&gt; &amp;amp; Cross, E. (2015). Can time-based decay explain temporal distinctiveness effects in task switching? &lt;em&gt;Quarterly Journal of Experimental Psychology, 68&lt;/em&gt;, 19&amp;ndash;45. &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.jimgrange.org/publication/Grange-temporal_distinctiveness/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;(Link)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Computational Cognitive Models</title>
      <link>/project/computational_models/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Feb 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/project/computational_models/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;p&gt;The ultimate goal in the field of cognitive science/psychology is to understand the workings of the human/animal mind. How do we selectively attend to goal-relevant stimuli? How do we remember such vast amounts of information? How do we plan and co-ordinate complex plans of action? Researchers address these problems by describing behaviour, through observation and experimentation. At a higher level, researchers aim to predict behaviour: Only a solid understanding of a phenomenon allows successful prediction of future behaviour in differing contexts. Prediction is a key tool for assessing whether our understanding of a phenomenon is sufficient.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Understanding cognitive phenomena is challenging as the human mind is impossibly complex; thus, researchers develop models of cognition, which abstract away from unnecessary details whilst emphasising details thought to underlie the phenomena under investigation. Examination of the modelís behaviour provides a window onto the more complex system that it is representing, increasing our understanding of that system.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Inspired by several outstanding theorists in my field, I am interested in applying models of cognition to experimental data to understand human behaviour in more detail. In particular, recent work in my lab has focussed on developing and testing models of inhibition during task switching. I am also interested in integrating task switching models with models that address other cognitive processes (such as memory models; see for example Grange &amp;amp; Cross, 2015).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We use these models to aid our understanding of cognition, with the aim of applying this knowledge to probing cognition in (for example) clinical and ageing populations.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;representative-publications&#34;&gt;Representative Publications&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Grange, J.A.&lt;/strong&gt;, Stephens, R., Jones, K., &amp;amp; Owen, L. (2016). The effect of alcohol hangover on choice response time. &lt;em&gt;Journal of Psychopharmacology, 30&lt;/em&gt;, 654&amp;ndash;661. &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.jimgrange.org/publication/Grange-hangover_rt/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;(Link)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;

&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Grange, J.A.&lt;/strong&gt; (2016). flankr: An R package implementing computational models of attentional selectivity. &lt;em&gt;Behavior Research Methods, 48&lt;/em&gt;, 528&amp;ndash;541. &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.jimgrange.org/publication/Grange-flankr/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;(Link)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;

&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Grange, J.A.&lt;/strong&gt; (2016). Temporal distinctiveness in task switching: Assessing the mixture-distribution assumption. &lt;em&gt;Frontiers in Cognition, 7&lt;/em&gt;:251. &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.jimgrange.org/publication/Grange-mixture_dist/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;(Link)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;

&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Grange, J.A.,&lt;/strong&gt; &amp;amp; Cross, E. (2015). Can time-based decay explain temporal distinctiveness effects in task switching? &lt;em&gt;Quarterly Journal of Experimental Psychology, 68&lt;/em&gt;, 19&amp;ndash;45. &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.jimgrange.org/publication/Grange-temporal_distinctiveness/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;(Link)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;

&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Grange, J.A.,&lt;/strong&gt; &amp;amp; Houghton, G. (2014). Models of cognitive control in task switching. In J.A. Grange &amp;amp; G.Houghton (Eds.), &lt;em&gt;Task switching and cognitive control&lt;/em&gt;. New York, NY: Oxford University Press. &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.jimgrange.org/publication/grange-task_switching_book_models/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;(Link)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;

&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Grange, J.A.,&lt;/strong&gt; Juvina, I., &amp;amp; Houghton, G. (2013). On costs and benefits of n&amp;ndash;2 repetition costs in task switching: Toward a behavioral marker of cognitive inhibition. &lt;em&gt;Psychological Research, 77&lt;/em&gt;, 211&amp;ndash;222. &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.jimgrange.org/publication/grange-costs_benefits_inhibition_model/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;(Link)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cognition in Clinical &amp; Ageing Populations</title>
      <link>/project/clinical_applications/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Feb 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/project/clinical_applications/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;p&gt;Much of our work has focussed on basic questions on cognitive psychology. More recently, we have shifted our attention to some more applied questions, and it is our aim to increase our focus on this line of research. We aim to utilise the findings from our basic research programme to probe cognition in clinical and ageing populations.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;representative-publications&#34;&gt;Representative Publications&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Grange, J.A.&lt;/strong&gt;, &amp;amp; Becker, R. (2018). The effect of aging on response congruency in task switching. &lt;em&gt;Journals of Gerentology Series B: Psychological Sciences &amp;amp; Social Sciences&lt;/em&gt;, in press. &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.jimgrange.org/publication/Grange-congruency_meta/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;(Link)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;

&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Martini, A., Ellis, S.J., &lt;strong&gt;Grange, J.A.,&lt;/strong&gt; Tamburin, S., Dal Lago, D., Vianello, G., &amp;amp; Edelstyn, N.M.J. (2018). Risky decision-making and affective features of impulse control disorder in Parkinson&amp;rsquo;s disease. &lt;em&gt;Journal of Neural Transmission, 125&lt;/em&gt;, 131-143. &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.jimgrange.org/publication/Martini-2018/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;(Link)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;

&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Stephens, R., Holloway, K., &lt;strong&gt;Grange, J.A.,&lt;/strong&gt; Jones, K., &amp;amp; Owen, L. (2017). Does familial risk for alcohol use disorder predict alcohol hangover? &lt;em&gt;Psychopharmacology, 234&lt;/em&gt;, 1795-1802. &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.jimgrange.org/publication/Stephens-familial_risk/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;(Link)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;

&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Edelstyn, N.M.J., &lt;strong&gt;Grange, J.A.,&lt;/strong&gt; Ellis, S.J., &amp;amp; Mayes, A.M. (2016). A deficit in familiarity-driven recognition in a right-sided mediodorsal thalamic lesion patient. &lt;em&gt;Neuropsychology, 30&lt;/em&gt;, 213-214. &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.jimgrange.org/publication/Edelstyn-familiarity_parkinsons/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;(Link)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Scientific Reproducibility &amp; Replication</title>
      <link>/project/scientific_reproducibility/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/project/scientific_reproducibility/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;p&gt;Replication is the most important statistic. If an experimental effect does not replicateóeither in your own lab or independentlyóthen trust in that effect should rightly diminish. Thus, assessing the reproducibility of an effect should rightly be among the priorities of psychological scientists. Despite the importance, replication attempts in psychology are rare, likely due to the enhanced incentive (e.g. publications, grant income) to introduce new ideas to the field rather than assess the validity of old ones.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I was involved in the work conducted by the Open Science Collaboration, which was published in the journal &lt;em&gt;Science&lt;/em&gt; in 2015. This paper was a large-scale, world-wide collaborative effort to systematically examine the rate and predictors of reproducibility in psychological science. The collaboration  attempted to replicate 100 studies published in three prominent psychology journals in 2008, with the aim of calculating an empirical rate of replication, as well as investigating factors that predict reproducibility. The news wasn&amp;rsquo;t pretty: Reproducibility in psychological science is low.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I have been involved in several published projects working on improving reproducibility in psychological science. I also have ongoing work looking factors that might influence reproducibility in work more closely related to my own, and how to improve these factors. More on this soon&amp;hellip;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;representative-publications&#34;&gt;Representative Publications&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Lakens, D., Adolfi, F., Albers, C.,&amp;hellip; &amp;hellip;&lt;strong&gt;Grange, J.A.,&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;hellip; &amp;hellip;&amp;amp; Zwaan, R. (2018). Justify your alpha. &lt;em&gt;Nature Human Behavior&lt;/em&gt;. &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.jimgrange.org/publication/Lakens-2018/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;(Link)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;

&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Anderson, C. J.,Bahnik, S., Barnett-Cowan, M.,&amp;hellip; &amp;hellip;&lt;strong&gt;Grange, J.A.&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;hellip; &amp;hellip; &amp;amp; Zuni, K. (2016). Response to a comment on ìEstimating the reproducibility of psychological scienceî. &lt;em&gt;Science, 351,&lt;/em&gt; 1037. &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.jimgrange.org/publication/Anderson-2016-OSC_reply/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;(Link)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;

&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Open Science Collaboration&lt;/strong&gt;. (2015). Estimating the reproducibility of psychological science. &lt;em&gt;Science, 349&lt;/em&gt;, 943. &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.jimgrange.org/publication/OSC-science_article/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;(Link)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;

&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Open Science Collaboration&lt;/strong&gt;. (2013). The Reproducibility Project: A model of large-scale collaboration for empirical research on reproducibility. In V. Stodden, F. Leisch, &amp;amp; R. Peng (Eds.), &lt;em&gt;Implementing Reproducible Computational Research (A Volume in the R Series)&lt;/em&gt;, New York, NY: Taylor &amp;amp; Francis. &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.jimgrange.org/publication/OSC-book_chapter/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;(Link)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;

&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Open Science Collaboration.&lt;/strong&gt; (2012). An open, large-scale, collaborative effort to estimate the reproducibility of psychological science. &lt;em&gt;Perspectives on Psychological Science, 7,&lt;/em&gt; 657-670. &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.jimgrange.org/publication/OSC-estimating_reproducibility/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;(Link)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Justify your alpha</title>
      <link>/publication/lakens-2018/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jan 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/publication/lakens-2018/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The effect of aging on response congruency in task switching: A meta-analysis.</title>
      <link>/publication/grange-congruency_meta/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jan 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/publication/grange-congruency_meta/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Risky decision-making and affective features of impulse control disorder in Parkinson’s disease</title>
      <link>/publication/martini-2018/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/publication/martini-2018/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Inhibition in task switching: The reliability of the n−2 repetition cost</title>
      <link>/publication/kowalczyk-inhition_reliability/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Jan 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/publication/kowalczyk-inhition_reliability/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The effect of episodic retrieval on inhibition in task switching</title>
      <link>/publication/episodic_retrieval/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Jan 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/publication/episodic_retrieval/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Does familial risk for alcohol use disorder predict alcohol hangover?</title>
      <link>/publication/stephens-familial_risk/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Jan 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/publication/stephens-familial_risk/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Example Talk</title>
      <link>/talk/example-talk/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Jan 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/talk/example-talk/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Embed your slides or video here using &lt;a href=&#34;https://sourcethemes.com/academic/post/writing-markdown-latex/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;shortcodes&lt;/a&gt;. Further details can easily be added using &lt;em&gt;Markdown&lt;/em&gt; and $\rm \LaTeX$ math code.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A deficit in familiarity-driven recognition in a right-sided mediodorsal thalamic lesion patient</title>
      <link>/publication/edelstyn-familiarity_parkinsons/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Feb 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/publication/edelstyn-familiarity_parkinsons/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Temporal distinctiveness in task switching: Assessing the mixture-distribution assumption.</title>
      <link>/publication/grange-mixture_dist/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Feb 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/publication/grange-mixture_dist/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>flankr: An R package implementing computational models of attentional selectivity</title>
      <link>/publication/grange-flankr/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Jan 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/publication/grange-flankr/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
