<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Projects on Jim Grange</title>
    <link>/project/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Projects on Jim Grange</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>&amp;copy; 2018</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 17 Feb 2018 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/project/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Cognitive Control Processes</title>
      <link>/project/cognitive_control/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Feb 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/project/cognitive_control/</guid>
      <description>Current Projects: Task Switching
Memory &amp;amp; Cognitive Control
Task Switching Humans live in an increasingly busy, multi-task environment which often requires frequent switching between different cognitive operations and tasks. Driving, for example, presents us with an incredibly complex environment wherein many sub-tasks&amp;mdash;e.g. speed monitoring, interpretation of abstract road signs, planning the best route etc.&amp;mdash;must be organised and deployed appropriately in order to arrive at our destination safely. Yet, despite the complexity, humans are able to act efficiently in a goal-directed manner.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cognition in Clinical &amp; Ageing Populations</title>
      <link>/project/clinical_applications/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Feb 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/project/clinical_applications/</guid>
      <description> Representative Publications </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Computational Cognitive Models</title>
      <link>/project/computational_models/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Feb 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/project/computational_models/</guid>
      <description>The ultimate goal in the field of cognitive science/psychology is to understand the workings of the human/animal mind. How do we selectively attend to goal-relevant stimuli? How do we remember such vast amounts of information? How do we plan and co-ordinate complex plans of action? Researchers address these problems by describing behaviour, through observation and experimentation. At a higher level, researchers aim to predict behaviour: Only a solid understanding of a phenomenon allows successful prediction of future behaviour in differing contexts.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Scientific Reproducibility &amp; Replication</title>
      <link>/project/scientific_reproducibility/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/project/scientific_reproducibility/</guid>
      <description> Representative Publications </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>